var questions = [
    {
        question: "How many centuries does Virat Kohli have in ODI ?",
        choices: ["12", "20", "28", "31"],
        answer: "28"
        },

    {
        question: "Which team did win the IPL 2017 trophy ?",
        choices: ["Mumbai", "Delhi", "Kolkata", "Banglore"],
        answer: "Mumbai"
        },
    {
        question: "Which year did Sachin play his last Internation Game?",
        choices: ["2010", "2014", "2013", "2015"],
        answer: "2013"
        },
    {
        question: "What is Dhoni's middle Name?",
        choices: ["Kumar", "Rajput", "Singh", "Jain"],
        answer: "Singh"
        },
    {
        question:"Who has scored highest number of Double Centuries in Test Cricket ?",
        choices:["Kumar Sangakara","Don Bradman","Virat Kohli","Sachin Tendulkar"],
        answer:"Don Bradman"
    },
    {
        question:"Who is the second highest run scorer in ODI Cricket ?",
        choices:["Ricky Ponting","Jack Kalis","Saurav Ganguly","Kumar Sangakara"],
        answer:"Kumar Sangakara"
    },
    {
        question:"Who has scored highest no of Sixes in ODI Cricket",
        choices:["Virendar Sehwag","Gayle","Shahid Afridi","Ms.Dhoni"],
        answer:"Shahid Afridi"
    },
    {
        question:"Against which team in ODI, Rohit Sharma had scored 264 Runs ?",
        choices:["Srilanka","Australia","England","South Africa"],
        answer:"Srilanka"
    },
    {
        question:"Which cricketers have the record for the highest run patnership at the World Cup ?",
        choices:["Sachin Tendulkar and Saurav Ganguly","Saurav Ganguly and Rahul Dravid","Saurav Ganguly and Virender Sehwag","Rahul Dravid and Sachin Tendulkar"],
        answer:"Saurav Ganguly and Rahul Dravid"
    },
    {
        question:"Which country hosted 2015â€“Cricket World Cup ?",
        choices:["India","Australia","New Zeland","Both (B) and (C)"],
        answer:"Both (B) and (C)"
    },
    {
        question:"Which country has won the ICC Twenty-20 World Cup Cricket played in May 2010 ? ",
        choices:["Sri Lanka","England","India","Australia"],
        answer:"England"
    },
    {
        question:"The highest wicket taker in test matches is now-",
        choices:["Shane Warne","Muthia Murlitharan","Kapil Dev","Dennis Lillee"],
        answer:"Muthia Murlitharan"
    }
]
var question2=[
    
]